[
  {
    "questionNo": "Q1",
    "question": "If Zara’s family decided to stay for 7 days in the village, which of the following is the cardinal number for 7?",
    "options": [
      "Seven",
      "Fifteen",
      "Twenty",
      "Seventy"
    ],
    "correct": 0
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q2",
    "question": "Zara’s family packed 40 snacks for the journey. Which number shows how many snacks they packed?",
    "options": [
      "Four",
      "Forty",
      "Fourteen",
      "Fifty"
    ],
    "correct": 1
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q3",
    "question": "If Zara and her family travelled for 50 kilometres to reach the village, how would you write 50 in words?",
    "options": [
      "Fifteen",
      "Fifty",
      "Fifth",
      "Five"
    ],
    "correct": 1
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q4",
    "question": "They are going to visit 10 tourist spots in the village. What is the cardinal number for 10?",
    "options": [
      "Twentieth",
      "Tenth",
      "Ten",
      "Eighth"
    ],
    "correct": 2
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q5",
    "question": "They packed a total of 25 clothes for the trip. Which of the following is the correct cardinal number for 25?",
    "options": [
      "Thirty",
      "Twenty",
      "Fifteen",
      "Twenty-five"
    ],
    "correct": 3
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q6",
    "question": "Zara packed 18 books for her trip. Which number shows how many books she packed?",
    "options": [
      "Eight",
      "Eighteen",
      "Eighteen-five",
      "Eighty"
    ],
    "correct": 1
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q7",
    "question": "They visited 9 different shops in the village. What is the cardinal number for 9?",
    "options": [
      "Ninth",
      "Nine",
      "Nineteenth",
      "Tenth"
    ],
    "correct": 1
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q8",
    "question": "Zara packed 20 souvenirs for her trip. Which of the following is the correct cardinal number for 20?",
    "options": [
      "Twenty-one",
      "Twenty-five",
      "Twenty",
      "Ten"
    ],
    "correct": 2
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q9",
    "question": "Zara took 12 postcards from the village. Which option shows how many postcards she took?",
    "options": [
      "Twelve",
      "Thirteen",
      "One",
      "Eleven"
    ],
    "correct": 0
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q10",
    "question": "They packed 28 apples for her journey. Which of the following is the correct cardinal number for 28?",
    "options": [
      "Twenty-eight",
      "Twenty",
      "Thirty",
      "Twenty-five"
    ],
    "correct": 0
  }
]
